<?xml version="1.0"?>
<playlist version="1" xmlns="http://xspf.org/ns/0/">
    <title>Random</title>
    <trackList>
        <track>
            <title>The Office</title>
            <annotation>A clip from the office</annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=excBsIv_3xI</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Some office video</title>
            <annotation>Another clip from youtube</annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sA1qEckOkP8</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Powerthirst</title>
            <annotation>	 Energy drink for people that need gratuitous amounts of energy! SPORTS you\&apos;ll be good at them!! RARRRRRRR!! With all new flavors like SHOCKLATE!! Chocolate energy!! Its like adding chocolate to an ELECTRICAL STORM!! If you like Strawberry...How about RAWBERRY!!! Made with lightning!! REAL LIGHTNING!!!!!! You\&apos;ll have energy running all the time!! Power lifting, power sleeping, power dating, power spawning babies!!! You will have soo many babies! 400 babies!!!! Then you feed Shocklate to your babies and they\&apos;ll become good at SPORTS!! And they\&apos;ll run ABNORMALLY FAST! They\&apos;ll compete against Kenyans, they\&apos;ll run as fast as Kenyans, they\&apos;ll run past people that think they\&apos;re Kenyans, then there\&apos;ll be a tie and they\&apos;ll be deported back to KENYA!!! You\&apos;ll be moving soo fast mother nature will be like SlOw DoWn! And you\&apos;ll be like FUCK YOU and kick her in the face with your ENERGY LEGS!!! Be smart don\&apos;t gamble on your energy. SNAKE EYES!!! </annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qRuNxHqwazs</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Summer Heights High - Crumpet</title>
            <annotation>Mr G Has An Imaginary Friend Called Crumpet!! </annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t94irm-clEw</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Justive - D.A.N.C.E</title>
            <annotation>Justice\&apos;s video to D.A.N.C.E</annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RpvNNJvww2A</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Dramatic Chipmunk</title>
            <annotation>The best 5 second clip on the internet. </annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a1Y73sPHKxw</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Old Gregg</title>
            <annotation>Old Gregg (originally posted on Youtube by philisdead4) is a fictional character portrayed by Noel Fielding. He was created for the \&quot;The Legend of Old Gregg\&quot;, a 2005 episode of the TV series, The Mighty Boosh. He later went on to appear in the 2006 stage show, The Mighty Boosh. The name of the character is derived from an incident where a friend of Julian Barratt and Noel Fielding\&apos;s, while at a festival in the middle of the night, heard a girl named Jessi Kennedy yelling \&quot;I\&apos;m Old Gregg!\&quot;.  Old Gregg is a transsexual merman who occasionally refers to his vagina (which emits a blinding light) as his \&quot;mangina.\&quot; He inhabits a cave below the lake in a village called Black Lake. Old Gregg is extremely fond of Bailey\&apos;s Irish Cream, as well as being a watercolor painter. Old Gregg falls in love with Howard, even though Howard is annoyed with him. He sings a song with him entitled \&quot;Love Games\&quot;, chronicling his obsession and Howard\&apos;s reluctance.  Old Gregg is first seen in the 2005 episode, \&quot;The Legend of Old Gregg\&quot; in which he meets and falls in love with Howard; who is then rescued by Vince. Old Gregg then joins Howard in the 2006 stage show, after tracking him down and having himself delivered in a box, where they sing a rendition of \&quot;Love Games\&quot; and are later seen kissing. Old Gregg last appeared in deleted scene from the 2007 episode, \&quot;Party\&quot;, disguised as a woman who has taken a liking to Howard. </annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ApGIl6dul_w</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Maths</title>
            <annotation>The largest number is 45 billion- though mathematicians suspect there may be even larger numbers.</annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=drE5cHe6c3s</location>
        </track>
        <track>
            <title>Naughty Girl</title>
            <annotation>She\&apos;s a naughty girl with a bad habit for drugs.</annotation>
            <location>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GrXvF5JlmRM</location>
        </track>
    </trackList>
</playlist>